Guide to the Alan Pryce-Jones Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1876-1996; Series I; 11.5; (28 boxes)
  - ALAN PRYCE-JONES CORRESPONDENCE
    - Bullock, Malcolm, 1946-66, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 210)
      Undated postcard is photograph
      of APJ and an unidentified man
    - Bulmer-Thomas, Ivor (Ivor Thomas), 1949 Oct 10 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Bülow, Claus von
      See: Von Bülow, Claus, Box 24, folder 1245
    - Bunting, Josiah, 1976 Nov 8 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Burkhart, Charles, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Burns, T. F., 1960-67 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Butler, E. M., 1947-49 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Butler, Ewan, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 216)
      Accompanied by synopsis titled
      "The Poisoned Pen: a History of
      Black
    - Butler, Rohan d'Olier, 1948 Sep 24 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Butterfield, Herbert, Sir, 1954-55 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Byron, Robert, 1931-37, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Byrne, John, 1989-96, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 220)
      See also: Bertram Rota Ltd., Box 2, folder 101
    - "C" general, 1925-94, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 221-222)
    - Caccia, Harold, Sir; Caccia, Nancy, 1958-83, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Caetani, Marguerite, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Caiger, Steve, 1983-84, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1950 Oct 27 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - Calder, Robert, 1976-82 (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Calder-Marshall, Arthur, 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Callimachi, Anne-Marie Vacaresco, Princess, 1954-69 (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - Calvocoressi, Peter, 1954-81 (Box 6, Folder 230)
      See also: Chatto and Windus, Box 7, Folder 255
    - Cameron, J. M., 1948 Jan 14 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Campbell, Roy, [1952-56], n.d. (Box 7, Folder 232)
      Letter of 1954 is accompanied
      by two letters of conveyance,
      one from A. S. Frere of William
      Heineman Ltd. and one from
      Sir William Haley; several
      letters accompanied by drafts
      of reviews and poems
    - Campbell, Shelagh, 1987 Apr 5, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Candolle, Roger de, 1954-87, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 234-235)
      Accompanied by copies of letters
      from de Candolle to Ian Whigham,
      Patersons Snow & Co. (Eland Hore
      Patersons), Harris Upham & Co.,
      John Dubé, and David Pryce-Jones
    - Canfield, Cass, 1963 Sep 11 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Caraman, Philip
      See: The Month, Box 15, Folder 827
    - Carey, Gary, 1972, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Carr, Raymond
      See: St. Antony's College, Oxford, Box 22, Folder 1084
    - Carter, A. C. R., 1948-49 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Carey, Joyce
      See: Jay Mallory, Box 14, Folder 774
    - Case, Margaret, 1972, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 239)
      Accompanied by a letter of
      conveyance from her attorney,
      Edwin B. Colwell to APJ
    - Casson, Hugh Maxwell, Sir, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Cassan, Antoine, 1975, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Cavendish, Elizabeth, Lady, 1954-83, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Cecil, David, Lord, 1932-58, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Celovsky, Boris, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - The Century Association (New York, N.Y.), 1961-93 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Champlin, Marjorie Weeden, 1984-88 (Box 7, Folder 246)
      Accompanied by a copy of
      a letter from Bruce Howe to
      Champlin, and one from her
      to The New York Times.
    - Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Channon, Henry, Sir ("Chips"), 1978 Mar (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Channon, Paul, 1958, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Chaplin, Anthony Freskin Charles Hamby, Viscount, 1951 Feb 21 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Chapman, Grace, 1932-60 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Chapman, R. W., 1937-58 (Box 7, Folder 252)
      Letter of 1954 Sep 30 is
      accompanied by a letter
      to Chapman from H. W. Garrod
    - Char, René, 1953, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Charteris, Hugo, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Chatto & Windus, 1947-64 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Cheltenham Festival of Literature, 1954-62 (Box 7, Folder 256)
      Accompanied by printed poem,
      "Gloucestershire Exile" by
      Sidney E. Knight
    - Chester Music, 1983-89 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - Chetwode, Penelope, 1948-85, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Chevalier, Gabriel, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Cholmondeley, George Horatio Charles Cholmondeley, Marquess of, 1954 Aug 7 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Chotzinoff, Samuel, 1957-63 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Christian-Howard, Anthony, 1971, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Church, Richard, 1950-65, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Churchill, Randolph Spencer, 1957 Jun 22 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Churchill, Winston Spencer, 1968 Jul 4 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Churchill, Winston, Sir, 1929 Jul 9 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - Chwat, Jacques, 1963, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Clarey, John, 1984-89, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Clark, Alan, 1960 Apr 3, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Clark, Kenneth, 1949 Nov 19 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Claudel, Paul, 1953 Mar 14 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Clayre, Alasdair, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1977 Sep 20 (Box 7, Folder 273)
      Accompanied by a copy of a
      letter from Cecil Day Lewis
      to Clemens
    - Clinton-Baddeley, V. C.
      See: Hadley, Patrick, Box 10, Folder 514
    - Clive, Mary, 1971 Jun 15 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - Closseu, Georg, 1970, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - Cobbett, Walter Willson, 1929-30 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - Cochran, Charles Blake, Sir, 1932 May 17 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Cockerell, Sydney Carlyle, Sir, 1948-57, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - Cocteau, Jean, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Coe, Kenton, 1962-85, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Coghill, Nevill, 1954 Dec 18 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Cohen, Marvin, 1962 Jun 15, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Colefax, Sybil, 1947-49, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Coles, S. F. A., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Collingwood, Charles, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Collins, Vere H., 1957 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Collins Publishers, 1943-85 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Colquhoun, Archibald, 1946-58 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Commager, Henry Steele, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Communist Party (Executive Committee, London), 1948 Mar 17 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Compton-Burnett, Ivy, 1949-59 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Connelly, Marc, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Connolly, Cyril, 1941-46, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - Conquest, Robert, 1958 Feb 10 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - Contact Publications Limited, 1949 Aug 19 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Cooper, Diana, Lady, 1953-82, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - Cooper, Douglas, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - Cooper, Duff, Viscount Norwich, 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Cooper, Martin, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Cooper, Michele F., 1976 Aug 30 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Cornford, Frances Darwin, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - The Cornhill Magazine, 1943-53, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Cothill House, 1943-44 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Coward, Noël, 1961 Aug 17 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Cowell, Frank Richard, 1955 Dec 5 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Cowles, Fleur, 1960-61, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Cowley, Malcolm
      See: Viking Press, Box 24, Folder 1240
    - Crankshaw, Edward, 1945-67 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Cravath, Swaine & Moore, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Creston, Dormer (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Crevel, René, [ca. 1932] (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Crewe, Quentin, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Critchett, Dan, 1981-83, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - The Critical Quarterly, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Critique, 1948-50 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Crocker, Walter R., 1953 May 23 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Croft-Cooke, Rupert, 1968 Jun 15 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Cromer, Ruby, 1954-61, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Crook, Arthur, 1961-78, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 318)
      See also: The Times, Box 24, Folder 1202
    - Crosland, Susan, 1985 Nov 12 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Crozier, Eric, 1949 Feb 27 (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Cukor, George, 1962-65 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Cummings, E. E., 1954 Jul 22 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Cunard, Victor, 1946-59, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - Curtis Brown Ltd., 1949-87 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - "D" general, 1926-94 (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - Daily News (London), 1987 Mar 10 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - The Daily Telegraph, 1988-90 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - Dainton, F. S., 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - Damlos, Jack, 1980-82 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - Daniel, Clifton, 1984 Jan 27 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - Darby, H. C., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - D'Arcy, Martin Cyril, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - Darwin, Bernard, 1924-48 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Davenport, Marcia, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - David, Villiers, 1954 May 7 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - Davidson, Basil, 1949 Sep 5 (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - Davidson, Bruce; Davidson, Frances, 1961 Nov 19 (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - D'Avigdor Goldsmid, Henry, 1943-68 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - D'Avigdor Goldsmid, Rosemary, [1963-87], n.d. (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Dawkins, R. M., 1947 Jan 20 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Dawnay, Alan, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - Dawnay, Victoria, Lady, 1913-21, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 342-343)
    - Dawson, Christopher, 1944-48, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - Day Lewis, Cecil, 1959 Feb 24 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - De Bary, Anna, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - De Combray, Richard, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - Delafield, E. M., 1932 Jul 9 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - De La Mare, Walter, 1948-53 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - De-la-Noy, Michael, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - De Zoete, Beryl, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - Dickinson, Patric, 1950-60, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - Dickson, Lovat, 1959-63 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - Dix, George, 1962-90, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - Dobrée, Bonamy, 1955 Nov 5 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - Dorn, Marion, 1962 Jan 31 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Doubleday and Company, Inc., 1982 Jul 15 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Douglas, Alfred Bruce, Lord, 1932-44 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Driberg, Tom, 1958 Jul 1 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Driver, Godfrey Rolles, 1954 Oct 25 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Drogheda, Garrett Moore, Earl of; Drogheda, Joan Moore, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Dru, Alick; Dru, Gabriel Herbert, 1948-60, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Duckworth (firm), 1948-74 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Duff, Juliet, Lady, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - Dufour Editions, 1964 Aug 5 (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - Dugdale, Blanche E. C., n.d. (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - Dugdale, Michael, 1929-52, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - Duggan, Alfred Leo, 1953 Jul 16 (Box 9, Folder 368)
    - Duke, Doris, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 369)
    - Dulwich Picture Gallery, 1986 Mar 11 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - Duncan, Frank, 1969-71, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - Du Pont, Henry Francis, 1961-66 (Box 9, Folder 372)
    - Durrell, Lawrence, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 373)
    - Dyson, A. E.
      See: The Critical Quarterly, Box 8, Folder 313
    - "E" general, 1925-96, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 374)
    - Eady, Kelly (Kellog), 1963 Apr 22, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 375)
    - Ede, H. S. ("Jim"), 1963 Jan 14 (Box 9, Folder 376)
    - Eden, Clarissa, 1954-56, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 377)
    - Editions des Trois Collines, 1950 Jan 9 (Box 9, Folder 378)
    - Edward Arnold (Publishers) Ltd., 1962 Apr 12 (Box 9, Folder 379)
    - Edward Hulton Book Publishers, 1958 Aug 6 (Box 9, Folder 380)
    - Edward, John, 1941-48 (Box 9, Folder 381)
    - Einsiedel, Wolfgang von, 1947 Nov 3 (Box 9, Folder 382)
    - Eliot, Betty, 1965, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 383)
    - Eliot, T. S., 1943-59, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 384)
    - Elliot, Walter, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - Emery, Jane (Jane Novak), 1985-91 (Box 9, Folder 386)
      Accompanied by a typescript
      copy of her introduction to Rose Macaulay: a Writer's Life
    - Emery, Lin, 1962-94, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - Emmanuel, Pierre, 1953 Mar 9, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - Empson, William, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Encounter, 1959 Jul 9 (Box 9, Folder 390)
      See also: Stephen Spender, Box 23, folder 1140
    - The English-Speaking Union, 1984-91 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Enright, D. J., 1949-59 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - The Epilepsy Foundation, 1963-84 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Erle, Peter, 1942-49, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Ernle, Rowland Edmund Prothero, Baron, 1932 Jun 8 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - Esher, Lionel Gordon Baliol Brett, 4th Viscount, 1947 Jul 28 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Essays in Criticism, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Eton College, 1936-54, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Evans, Illtud, 1961-67, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - Eyres-Monsell, Graham, 1937-86, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Eyres-Monsell, Joan, 19[32]-34, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 401-402)
    - "F" general, 1931-92, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr.; Fairbanks, Mary Lee, 1974-79, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 404)
      Christmas card for 1979
      includes photograph
    - Fallowell, Duncan, 1990 May 10 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Fane, Julian, 1960 Apr 25 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Faringdon, Alexander Gavin Henderson, Baron, 1942-63 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Fermor, Patrick Leigh, 1987 Feb 12 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Fielding, Temple; Fielding, Nancy; Fielding, Dodge, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - The Fine Art Society Ltd., 1978 Sep 20 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Fisher, M. F. K., 1969 Nov 15 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - FitzGibbon, Constantine, 1950 Jan 9, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - FitzRandolph, Helen, 1949-58 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Fleming, Ann, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Fleming, Ian, 1955 May 6 (Box 9, Folder 415)
    - Fletcher-Watson, James, 1960 Jun 22 (Box 9, Folder 416)
    - Forbes, Alastair, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 417)
    - Forbes, H. A. Crosby, 1977 Nov 11 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Ford, Brinsley, 1972 Sep 28 (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - The Ford Foundation, 1959-65, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 420)
    - Ford, Nanette, 1952, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 421)
    - Fordham, Sine, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 422)
    - Fordham University, 1963 Aug 20 (Box 9, Folder 423)
    - Forster, E. M., 1943-51 (Box 9, Folder 424)
    - Fothergill, John, 1930 Jan 9 (Box 9, Folder 425)
    - Fould-Springer, Max, 1940-82, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 426)
    - France. Ministère des Affaires étrangères, 1953 Nov 24 (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - Franklin, David (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - Fraser, Antonia, 1956-82 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - Fraser, George, 1949-56 (Box 9, Folder 430)
    - Frazer & Haws Ltd., 1947-66 (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - Freeman, David, 1984-87 (Box 10, Folder 432)
    - Freemantle, Anne, 1938-75, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 433)
    - Freud, Ernst L., 1951 Mar 21 (Box 10, Folder 434)
    - The Frick Collection, 1973, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 435)
    - Fulford, Roger, 1946-71 (Box 10, Folder 436)
    - Fuller, John, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 437)
    - Fuller, Roy, 1950-59 (Box 10, Folder 438)
    - "G" general, 1920-93 (Box 10, Folder 439-440)
    - Gaines, Charles, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 441)
    - Gaitskell, Hugh; Gaitskell, Dora, 1953-63 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    - Gale Research Inc., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - Gambit Incorporated, 1970-75 (Box 10, Folder 444)
    - Garbett, Cyril, 1950 Sep 12 (Box 10, Folder 445)
    - Gardner, Martin, 1960 Jul 16 (Box 10, Folder 446)
    - The Garrick Club, 1979-96 (Box 10, Folder 447)
    - Gascoyne, David, 1953 Oct 12 (Box 10, Folder 448)
    - Gathorne-Hardy, Edward, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 449)
    - Gathorne-Hardy, Jonathan, 1954 [Aug?] 15 (Box 10, Folder 450)
    - Gathorne-Hardy, Robert, 1947 Jul 7 (Box 10, Folder 451)
    - Gelber, Jack, 1960 Sep 7 (Box 10, Folder 452)
    - Gellhorn, Martha, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 453)
    - George Routledge and Sons, 1938 Dec 15 (Box 10, Folder 454)
    - Georgetown University Library, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - Gerhardie, William Alexander, 1951-60 (Box 10, Folder 456)
    - Germain, André (Box 10, Folder 457)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster, 1960 Sep 20 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - Ghyka, Matila Costiescu, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Giannini, David, 1968 Nov 30 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Gibbins, Doris
      See: Mercer, Doris, Box 15, folder 803
    - Gibson, Joy Leslie, [1987] (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - Gibson, Wilfred Wilson, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - Gielgud, John, Sir, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Giles, Brian, 1957 Feb 27, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Gillespie, Rollo, 1974-82 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Gilmour, Andrew, 1983-87, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 466)
    - Gilmour, Caroline; Gilmour, Ian, 19[64]-91, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 467)
      Christmas card for [1964]
      the Gilmours and their
      children
    - Girard, Didier, 1990 May 6 (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - Girouard, Richard; Girouard, Blanche, 1931-40, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - Glamour, 1964 Feb 12 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - Glendinning, Victoria, 1975-78 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Glenville, Peter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Glover, Eleanor, Lady, 1980-86 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Golding, Louis, 1958 May 12 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Goldring, Douglas, 1937-59 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Gooch, G. P., 1949-57 (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Goodman, Jean, 1975 Sep 14 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Goodman, Nelson, 1968 Dec 3 (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - Gordon, Archie (Marquess of Aberdeen), 1975-83 (Box 10, Folder 479)
      See also: British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC), Box 3, Folder 152
    - Gorell, Ronald Gorell Barnes, Baron, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - Gorer, Geoffrey, 1953 Nov 17 (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - Görres, Ida Friederike, 1963 Jul 24 (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - Gosling, Nigel, 1967 Mar 21 (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Gow, Andrew Sydenham Farrar, 1940-47 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Gowing, Lawrence, 1954 Jun 14 (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - Gowrie, Alexander Patrick Greysteil Ruthven, Earl of (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Graham, Ian, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - Grahame, Elspeth, 1932 Sep 25 (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - Grant, Douglas, 1961 Apr 26 (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Graves, Robert, 1943-56, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Great Britain. 4th Hussars, Officers Detail Camp, 1939-40 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Great Britain. Foreign Office, 1947 Aug 5 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Great Britain. War Office, 1940-61 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Greene, Graham, 1948-59 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Green, Henry (Henry Vincent Yorke), 1929-51 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Green, Julien, 1951-55 (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Greenberg, Noah, 1960 Sep 6 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Grenier, Jean, 1936 Dec 13 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Griffin, Jonathan, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Grigson, Geoffrey, 1954-60 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Grimond, Jo, 1955-57 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Grindea, Miron, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Grisewood, Harman, 1966 Jul 24 (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - The Grolier Club, 1995 Feb 10 (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Gross, John, 1974-85 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Grunne, Dominic de, 1961-79, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Guinness, Bryan (Baron Moyne), 1956 Jul 15 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Guinness, Desmond, 1979-81 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Gunther, John, 1966 Jan 4 (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - "H" general, 1931-94 (Box 11, Folder 510-511)
    - H. J. Heinz Company, 1973 Sep 10 (Box 11, Folder 512)
    - Habsburg, Rosemary von, Archduchess of Austria, Princess of Salm-Salm, 1946 Mar 5 (Box 11, Folder 513)
    - Hadley, Patrick, 1940-43 (Box 11, Folder 514)
      Accompanied by a letter to Hadley
      from V. C. Clinton-Baddeley, with
      forwarding note to APJ
    - Haffenden, John, 1981-81 (Box 11, Folder 515)
    - Hahn, Reynaldo, 1934-37, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 516)
    - Hailsham of Marylebone, Quintin Hogg, Baron, 1956 Jan 23 (Box 11, Folder 517)
    - Haldane, Charlotte Franken, 1962 Apr 14 (Box 11, Folder 518)
    - Hale, Lionel, 1961 Apr 6 (Box 11, Folder 519)
    - Haley, William, Sir, 1954-67 (Box 11, Folder 520)
    - Hall Associates, 1978-96 (Box 11, Folder 521)
    - Hall, Donald, 1954 Sep 21 (Box 11, Folder 522)
    - Halle, Kay, 1953-86 (Box 11, Folder 523)
    - Hallowell, John, 1965-79, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 524)
    - Halperin, John, 1995 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 525)
    - Hamilton, G. Rostrevor, 1954 Jul 25 (Box 11, Folder 526)
    - Hamilton, Hamish ("Jamie"), 1963-81, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 527)
      See also: Hamish Hamilton Ltd., Box 11, folder 528
    - Hamish Hamilton Ltd., 1963-87, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 528)
    - Hammelmann, Hanns A., 1957-63, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 529)
    - Hamnet, Nina, [ca. 1932] (Box 11, Folder 530)
    - Hansford-Johnson, Pamela, 1959-66 (Box 11, Folder 531)
    - Hanley, James, 1954 May 14 (Box 11, Folder 532)
    - Hannay, Neilson Campbell, 1959 Oct 22 (Box 11, Folder 533)
    - Hansom Books/ Books and Bookmen, 1973-75 (Box 11, Folder 534)
    - Harbert, John, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 535)
    - Harcourt Brace & World, 1931-69 (Box 11, Folder 536)
    - Harding, Gilbert, 1954 Dec 8 (Box 11, Folder 537)
      Accompanied by a letter to
      Harding from Harry Backhouse
    - Hardy, Henry, 1995 Feb 13 (Box 11, Folder 538)
    - Harewood, George Henry Hubert Lascelles, Earl of, 1948-49 (Box 11, Folder 539)
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1969 Apr 8 (Box 11, Folder 540)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1933-47 (Box 11, Folder 541)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1951-58 (Box 11, Folder 542)
    - Harriman, Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 543)
    - Harris, Kenneth, 1948-50, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 544)
    - Harris, Ruth, 1959-96, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 545)
    - Harrod, Dominick, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 546)
    - Harrod, Wilhelmine Margaret Eve Cresswell, Lady ("Billa"), 1935-93, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 547)
    - Harrod, Roy Forbes, Sir, 1951-69 (Box 11, Folder 548)
    - Hart-Davis, Duff, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 549)
    - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1932-65 (Box 11, Folder 550)
    - Hartley, L. P. (Leslie Poles), 1953-59, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 551)
    - Hartwell, William Michael Berry, Baron, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 552)
    - The Harvill Press Ltd., 1951-58 (Box 11, Folder 553)
    - Harwood, George, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 554)
    - Haslip, Joan, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 555)
    - Hassall, Christopher, 1953-58 (Box 11, Folder 556)
    - Hastings, Maurice, 1939 Aug 16 (Box 11, Folder 557)
    - Hastings, Michael, 1956-58 (Box 11, Folder 558)
    - Hastings, Selina, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 559)
    - Havelock-Allan, Anthony, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 560)
    - Haxton, Gerald, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 561)
    - Hayes, Richard, 1961-67, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 562)
    - Haynes, E. S. P., 1931-48 (Box 11, Folder 563)
    - Hayward, John, 1940-1954 (Box 11, Folder 564)
    - Hazzard, Shirley, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 565)
    - Head, Anthony, 1954 May 4 (Box 11, Folder 566)
    - Headlam, Cuthbert Morley, Sir, 1953 Oct 10 (Box 11, Folder 567)
    - Healey, R. M., 1993 Jul 15 (Box 11, Folder 568)
    - Heard, Gerald, 1931-32 (Box 11, Folder 569)
    - Heath-Stubbs, John Francis Alexander, 1948 Jul 7 (Box 11, Folder 570)
    - Hecht, Rosa; Hecht, Zoltan, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 571)
    - Heller, Erich, 1950 Apr 27 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Helpmann, Robert, Sir, 1942 Jan 30 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Hemphill, Christopher, 1982 Jan 27 (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Henderson, Nicholas, Sir (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Henriot, Emile, 1951 Aug 29 (Box 12, Folder 576)
    - Heppenstall, Rayner, 1943-59 (Box 12, Folder 577)
    - Herbert, A. P., Sir, 1934 Nov 8 (Box 12, Folder 578)
    - Herbert, Elizabeth Willard, [1940] Aug 7 (Box 12, Folder 579)
      Elizabeth Herbert from
      Elizabeth Bocock
      See also: Shaw-Stewart, Elizabeth, Box 22, Folder 1108
    - Herring, Robert, 1931-46, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 580)
    - Hesketh, Christian ("Kisty"), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 581)
    - Heyworth, Peter, 1962-86, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 582)
    - Hill, Anne (Lady Anne Gathorne-Hardy), 1978 Dec 5 (Box 12, Folder 583)
    - Hill, Christopher, 1949 Oct 24 (Box 12, Folder 584)